A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, International Health Policy and Practice Program, Accession 2001:049, SG 2 FA792
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, International Health Policy and Practice Program, Accession 2001:049, SG 2
1999-2000
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA792
5.32 Cubic Feet 14 letter document boxes.
Scope and Contents
Contains IHPP Program staff files including Harkness Fellowship applications and incoming and outgoing mail files for the period 1999-2000.
Arrangement
As received.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Commonwealth Fund records were donated to RAC in 1985. Record transfers began in 1986, and accruals continue. This material was transferred to RAC in 2001 and accessioned by RAC as 2001:049.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
- International Health Policy and Practice Program, 1999-2000; 1
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Michael J. Fett - Department of Health (99-001-AUS), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Jane E. Pirkis (99-002-AUS), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Judith E. Homeshaw - University of Tazmania (99-003-AUS), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Sharon R. Goldfield - University of Melbourne (99-004-AUS), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Paula Wilton - Department of Human Services (99-005-AUS), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Sharon Wilcox - Department of Human Services (99-006-AUS), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Jennifer M. Lewis (99-007-AUS), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Virginia A. Hart (99-008-AUS), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Anne Elizabeth McConville - North Derbyshire Health Authority (HF 00-001 UK), 2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Christopher McCabe - The University of Sheffield (HF 00-006 UK), 2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Andrew Philip Jones - Caerphilly County Borough Council (HF 00-009 UK), 2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Mark Exworthy - London School of Economics and Political Science (HF 00-010 UK), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Tony Maltby- University of Birmingham (HF 00-012 UK), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Martin Paul Anderson - University of Nottingham (HF 00-13 UK), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Stephen Peckam - Oxford Brookes University (HF 00-014 UK), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Alasadair Gordon Miller (HF 00-015-UK), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Johnathan Watson - Health Education Board for Scotland (HF 00-016 UK), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Elinor Mary Thompson - South and West Devon Health Authority (HF 00-017 UK), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Domhnall MacAuley - University of Ulster (HF 00-018 UK), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Catherine Guelbert - Withington Community Hospital Development (HF 00-019 UK), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Paul M. Wilson - University of York (HF 00-020 UK), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Richard Cookson - London School of Economics (HF 00-021 UK), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Katharine Jane Thomas - University of Sheffield, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Juliet Tizzard - Program Educational Trust, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Robert Anderson - University of Wales College of Medicine (HF 00-025 UK), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Judy Taylor - King's Fund (HF 00-026 UK), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Linda Jane McKie - Glascow Caledonian University (HF 00-027 UK), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Sarah Elizabeth Ann Lowe - Office for National Statistics (HF 00-029 UK), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Heather Ann Wilkinson - University of Stirling (HF 00-030 UK), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Nicholas McNulty - Redbridge and Waltham Forest Health Authority (HF 00-032 UK), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Jacqueline D. Paige - Freelance Journalist (HF 00-033 UK), Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Andrew Reed - Merton Sutton and Wandsworth Health Authority (HF 00-034 UK), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Kay Pattison - Department of Health (HF 00-036 UK), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Brenda Roe - North Cheshire Health (99-001 UK), 1999 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Paul Miller - University of Nottingham (99-002 UK), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Helen Chin (99-003 UK), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Steven J. Ersser - Oxford Brookes University (99-005 UK), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Elizabeth Hart - University of Nottingham (99-006 UK), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Marion Bain (99-007 UK), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Siobhan McCartney - Glascow Health Board (99-009 UK), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Rhidian Hughes - University of York (99-010 UK), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Andrew MacCallum - Guys and St. Thomas Hospital (99-011 UK), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Gail Findlay - Bedfordshire Health (99-012 UK), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Gurch Randhawa - University of Luton (99-013 UK), 1999 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Antoinette Pirie - West Herts NHS Trust (99-014 UK), 1999 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Paula Friend - Worthing and Southlands (99-015 UK), 1999 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Sandra Dodgson - Department of Health (99-016 UK), 1999 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Cynthia Farquhar - University of Auckland (99-005 NZ), 1999 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Suzanne Crengle - University of Aukland (99-008 NZ), 1999 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Fiona Catherine McTavish (99-017 NZ), 1999 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Colin T. Tukuitonga (99-018 NZ), 1999 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Craig Johnston (99-019 NZ), 1999 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - John Thwaites - Healthlink South (99-001 NZ), 1999 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Tutahanga Malcolm Douglas (99-002 NZ), 1999 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Frances Anne Hughes (99-003 NZ), 1999 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Gabrielle M. Keating - Ministry of Health (99-004 NZ), 1999 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Mary Margaret Dawson (99-004 NZ), 1999 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Paul Colin Hansen (99-006 NZ), 1999 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Linus Opara (99-xxx NZ), 1999 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Harkness Fellows - Applicants - Christopher Cunningham - Massey University (99-010 NZ), 1999 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Mail Files - Incoming, 1999 July (Box 7, Folder 61-62)
  - Mail Files - Incoming, 1999 August (Box 7, Folder 63-64)
  - Mail Files - Incoming, 1999 August (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Mail Files - Outgoing, 1999 August (Box 8, Folder 66-68)
  - Mail Files - Outgoing, 1999 August (Box 9, Folder 69-70)
  - Mail Files - Incoming, 1999 September (Box 9, Folder 71-73)
  - Mail Files - Outgoing, 1999 September (Box 10, Folder 74-78)
  - Mail Files - Outgoing, 1999 September (Box 11, Folder 79-82)
  - Mail Files - Incoming, 1999 October (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Mail Files - Incoming, 1999 October (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Mail Files - Outgoing, 1999 October (Box 12, Folder 85-87)
  - Mail Files - Incoming, 1999 November (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Mail Files - Incoming, 1999 November (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - Mail Files - Outgoing, 1999 November (Box 13, Folder 90-91)
  - Mail Files - Incoming, 1999 December (Box 13, Folder 92-93)
  - Mail Files - Outgoing, 1999 December (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - Mail Files - Outgoing, 1999 December (Box 14, Folder 95-96)